[Music]
[Music] Give me a
drink oh the
real one oh my
god oh my god the one with money give me a drink
once
ji
black brother
[laughter] it will be like this
look at
me
[bell sound]
koliya ke to
[music]
no peacock [music] a
different level guy shooting [
laughter]
ok people ok
jima
kalu to camera support nahi
[laughter] do
you
marry me say what you
like
money wala say no no
koliya no see koliya no see Munab
but the heart is completely
clean
owner
shooting
Bhagyava
no no no you deserve better this is wa dark
koliya [laughter]
look at the huiya ko guru [laughter] you are crazy ma marry me marry me girl marry me
shoot you go
saajni
re [song voice]
[song voice]
saajni
re
so bring the lip kiss scene
[music]
[laughter]
say Hari with love [music]
hurry up
[music] there is
camera
multiple bigness ka baba ka
grandson
you stay
[laughter]
go
you are
right  [laughter]
He was a man of a different level
[music]
Saale
red sari rehna
[laughter] Will you
tick
[laughter]
Bear
you are
red
[song voice]
Choli [music] If you do
n't get married then go to your
father-in-law
Babu
I am not getting married then
Babu there will be a
problem
oh brother oh Kaluda [laughter]
Mantra maar na man vyah karwaj [laughter]
ki puja kar
marriage cancel
attitude
Babu priest ke
dahi
you fun hi fun
[laughter] If you
spoil the mood then Mudraab look at me
then [laughter]
I will
not silently chant the mantra silently
silent
mantra
[laughter]
today is a danger
Swaha sindoor tiko yaad
[music]
sindoor tiko sindoor tiko
tikola
[laughter]
Deiya ka dekh bhi deva [music]
Drive it too
[music]
Not from Nokia but from Nokia set
Excel buy a car
[laughter] give it to you Babu
I give you a Hero cycle and
I have other cars too brother
[music]
khala  Hey aunt [laughter] you've eaten the
food, you're
holding it
here brother give me the mangalsutra to drink
brother look at the
mangalsutra
look at the mangalsutra [laughter] hey mangalsutra look at the mudiya hit the mudiya hit the mudiya hit the mudiya [laughter] have you seen
the pinosi
[laughter]
[music]
listen carefully the feeling my
player is
playing
[laughter]
ek vachnala
do [song voice] [
music]
give [song voice] give the stick to
give [song voice] give the
stick to give
[song voice]
[laughter]
both [song voice]
look at the number two promise in front of you [nasal sound]
[laughter]
look at
number three promise to beat
mother said even more than manava aunt said even more than manava
mother my mother okay more okay sister
's sister said no agree
sister-in-law it's
fun
[laughter] sister-in-law it's fun
[laughter]
no
[music]
scooty [song voice] if
not a car then at least a scooty
[Song voice] Gaadi re
peelal
phool badam
kale
[music]
not of almonds
[laughs]
pila ke
khoo
[song voice]
[music]
kha
[song voice]
[laughter]
chhan ki mari mari laan ka
khandaan
oh
seven number promise tail swear
[nasal sound]
Koiya seven
births
worry [laughs]
worry is amazing disgrace
eight number promise la promise oh Babu
Sarkar
eight number promise swear then boyfriend feed me
[laughs]
Dil khush
safety is important brother today
Babu Babu is settled comfortably oh sister
[laughter] do
n't say sorry Babu say point say point hey he has a
boyfriend
no no he doesn't know I don't know otherwise the
stuff will be done no no no
one is
just a peacock shoot everyone the
marriage is complete
[music]
go
[music] hey
boyfriend you are what if not
then get
married get it
say brother with love
that priest
[music]
ki [music] kajalgi
area yellow pagal utaki [
music] [music]
ki [
music] sing it I will sing it I will sing it
Tekki
[Music]
Take
money
but there is work, there is work, there is
work, no complaints, don't worry about empty
complaints,
earn money and work,
you don't waste your life,
you are a young
heroine, you are my life, I swear
Bhabhi, look at the hands of five people, as if they had
hands
[Music]
then get the expenses done
and hands of hands
[Music]
Hello
[Music] I don't want
you to spend it day and night without me
[Music] Khane [Song voice]
But
oh my god, there is no
expense, ma oh no, two, three, three,
Thailand, Dubai [Laughter] Goa, a
very useful
piece of work, oh
no, at
least you belonged to Bua's [Music] you are
also from the family,
Bua, marry me, work day and night,
love, love, love, okay, then
marry me, take a
drink
[Music]
yes, the
pain of the
expenses,
go
kiss me [Laughter] you have given me a
different level, yikes, make
me coma [Laughter]
okay
[Laughter]
revenge is definitely justice
[Music]